Guide to the Barney Rosset papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Files Used for Autobiography, 1936-2011
  - "Book II"
    - "Condensed Deposition," 2007 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - "Grove Press Film History," 2007 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - "Che Guevara," 2007 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Chapter Files
    - "Chapter 1--Ireland and Marquette," 2000s (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - "Chapter One--Ireland," 2007 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - "Chapter Two--Childhood in Marquette Chicago," 2007 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - "Chapter 2," 2006 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - "Chapter Three," 2007 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - "Chapter Five," 2007 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - "Chapter Six," 2007 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - "Chapter Six--Modern China Emerges," 2007 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - "Chapter Seven," 2007 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - "Chapter Eight--Strange Victory," 2007 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - "Chapter Nine--Joan: The Beginning," 2007-2009 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - "Chapter Ten--Strange Victory in Prague," 2007 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - "Chapter Eleven--Joan in NY," 2007 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - "Chapter 12--Beckett" 2007-2009 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - "Chapter 13--The Lady Shall Lead Us," 2007 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - "Chapter 14--Henry," 2007 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - "Rosset Postwar Chapter," 1940s (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - "Chicago to India," 1942-1946 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - "China Chapter--Outtakes and Research Materials," 1940s-2000s, (2 folders) (Box 68, Folder 8-9)
  - "China," 2006 Undated (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - "Chinese History--8th Grade," 1936 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - "Eleutheria--David Tucker," 2010 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - "Evergreen," 1970s-2000s (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - "Maurice Girodias," Undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - "IRELAND General Backround Material," 2004 Undated, (2 folders) (Box 68, Folder 15-16)
  - "Ireland Weston House Ballyforan Murder," 2005 Undated (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - "Irish Penal Records--Original and Copies," 2004 Undated (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - "Marquette Info," 1990s-2000s Undated (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Photographs
    - "Selected Evergreen & Black Cat Titles," Undated, (2 folders) (Box 68, Folder 20-21)
    - "Selected Grove Press, Part I," Undated (1 of 2 folders) (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - "Selected Grove Press, Part I," Undated (1 of 2 folders) (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - "Seleted Grove Press, Part II," Undated, (2 folders) (Box 69, Folder 2-3)
  - "Kushwant Singh," 2006 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - "Singh,"2007 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - "Talmer on Grove Drama," Undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - "Women's Lib and End of Grove," 2007 (Box 69, Folder 7)